{
    "rows": [{
        "question": "The picture that describes me the most is... ",
        "answer": "Abstract art ",
        "tag": "Front-facing"
    }, {
        "question": "The picture that describes me the most is... ",
        "answer": "Structured looking painting ",
        "tag": "Creative"
    }, {
        "question": "The picture that describes me the most is... ",
        "answer": "Colour but neat painting ",
        "tag": "Structured/Planning"
    }, {
        "question": "The picture that describes me the most is... ",
        "answer": "Black and white painting ",
        "tag": "Calm under pressure"
    }, {
        "question": "My handwriting usually looks like (choose from pictures)",
        "answer": "Readable, what matters is the content",
        "tag": "Detailed"
    }, {
        "question": "My handwriting usually looks like (choose from pictures)",
        "answer": "Completely not on the lines ",
        "tag": "Creative"
    }, {
        "question": "My handwriting usually looks like (choose from pictures)",
        "answer": "V neat penmanship type ",
        "tag": "Calm under pressure"
    }, {
        "question": "My handwriting usually looks like (choose from pictures)",
        "answer": "Messy because I love writing for many people",
        "tag": "Encouraging"
    }, {
        "question": "When at a brunch spot with my friends ",
        "answer": "I listen to what music they're playing ",
        "tag": "Observant"
    }, {
        "question": "When at a brunch spot with my friends ",
        "answer": "I am very particular about what food they have ",
        "tag": "Detailed"
    }, {
        "question": "When at a brunch spot with my friends ",
        "answer": "I think about what activity we're doing after ",
        "tag": "Structured/Planning"
    }, {
        "question": "When at a brunch spot with my friends ",
        "answer": "I check if they serve good coffee ",
        "tag": "Coffee"
    }, {
        "question": "My friends don't know that I... ",
        "answer": "Pretend to be introverted. I'm really more of an extrovert ",
        "tag": "Front-facing"
    }, {
        "question": "My friends don't know that I... ",
        "answer": "Secretly love excel sheets",
        "tag": "Detailed"
    }, {
        "question": "My friends don't know that I... ",
        "answer": "Am very particular about time",
        "tag": "Structured/Planning"
    }, {
        "question": "My friends don't know that I... ",
        "answer": "Am picky about how my coffee is made",
        "tag": "Coffee"
    }, {
        "question": "In V camp my favourite social activity is",
        "answer": "Worship sessions with my vg",
        "tag": "Behind"
    }, {
        "question": "In V camp my favourite social activity is",
        "answer": "Taking pictures with my vg",
        "tag": "Front-facing"
    }, {
        "question": "In V camp my favourite social activity is",
        "answer": "Tasting the food",
        "tag": "Observant"
    }, {
        "question": "In V camp my favourite social activity is",
        "answer": "The mass games",
        "tag": "Creative"
    }, {
        "question": "On free Fridays, I am most likely to...",
        "answer": "stay home and chill",
        "tag": "Behind"
    }, {
        "question": "On free Fridays, I am most likely to...",
        "answer": "Meet with a VG mate I know is going through a tough time",
        "tag": "Encouraging"
    }, {
        "question": "On free Fridays, I am most likely to...",
        "answer": "go wherever my friends are going",
        "tag": "Go with the flow/Adaptable"
    }, {
        "question": "On free Fridays, I am most likely to...",
        "answer": "Do something I already planned to do",
        "tag": "Structured/Planning"
    }, {
        "question": "My reaction when someone screams as he/she drops a hot cuppa is...",
        "answer": "check if they are OK and help them clean up",
        "tag": "Encouraging"
    }, {
        "question": "My reaction when someone screams as he/she drops a hot cuppa is...",
        "answer": "thank God it did not splash on them... and me",
        "tag": "Observant"
    }, {
        "question": "My reaction when someone screams as he/she drops a hot cuppa is...",
        "answer": "scream with them before anything",
        "tag": "Go with the flow/Adaptable"
    }, {
        "question": "My reaction when someone screams as he/she drops a hot cuppa is...",
        "answer": "check where the coffee was from",
        "tag": "Coffee"
    }, {
        "question": "Studying style?",
        "answer": "closet mug (there's been a robbery in my closet, but it's just me. I am the closet mugger)",
        "tag": "Behind"
    }, {
        "question": "Studying style?",
        "answer": "Study with friends and share notes",
        "tag": "Encouraging"
    }, {
        "question": "Studying style?",
        "answer": "Study what I can, if rabak also bopian",
        "tag": "Go with the flow/Adaptable"
    }, {
        "question": "Studying style?",
        "answer": "still got 4 whole days what, 1.5 topics a day not too bad\n",
        "tag": "Calm under pressure"
    }]
}
